Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Malhun.
Come on.
Come on Malhun!
Where are you headed?
Many will bleed today.
A day ago.
I will go to talk to
Manuel, the governor of Iznik, brother.
I am going to use trading to vanish them,
just like the way they want to vanish us.
I am going to offer him an opportunity
that none of the Lords would.
He is going to take it if he is smart.
He is going to face me if he is an idiot.
A man rises with his respondent, my Bey.
This agreement we are going to make with
the governor of Iznik will...
...enhance the trust level of Kayi Tent.
Osman Bey, all well and good but...
This is going to drive Lords crazy, right?
Lords are like rapid dogs, my Bala.
A wolf becomes a wolf when one thousand
dogs bark at him.
Infidels don't need reason to attack.
Their hostility is eternal.
They don't want us to settle down here,
to make this land our motherland.
This is why my Osman is going to
ruin them inside.
Evelallah (for sure).
My Bey, I want to join you if you allow.
Make preparations.
My Bey, the road is dangerous.
Lords must have heard you'll be on your
way to the governor.
Also, Malhun Hatun is with you.
I am worried that they may ambush you.
Our swords are hammered by heat, covered
with the blood of infidels, Bala Hatun.
We are going to overcome anything with
my Bey, Inshallah.
My Bey, what about the relic?
I am not taking it with me.
I'll have a different path from
the regular Iznik path.
Baykurt.
Prepare the horseshoe.
It's Osman Bey's command.
We are going to use Kızılhisar path
tomorrow.
The path will be rocky.
Eyvallah Head Alp.
Baykurt, no one should hear this.
Eyvallah (okay).
Orhan is entrusted to me, Malhun Hatun.
Don't worry.
May Allah bless you, Bala Hatun.
Long live my Bala, long live.
Can I come in my Bey?
Come.
I felt he wanted you, my Hatun.
I am starting the preparations for tomorrow,
Osman Bey.
I am going to set off.
The relic will stay in the tent.
Listen to me carefully.
It's your responsibility to protect
the tent, the relic, and my Orhan.
As you command, Osman Bey.
Tell me Gokce girl.
I heard that the relic
is staying in the tent.
Good job, Gokce.
Keep your eyes open.
Don't forget, they are going to be
punished for what they've done to you.
Fly then.
Say hi to Kosses.
Bilecik Castle.
Holy Jesus.
I don't deserve you.
I lost against the unbeliever infidels.
Holy Jesus.
I swear on you...
...I am going to...
...destroy them all.
- Sir.
- Come.
- Lord Nicola and Lord Kosses arrived sir.
- I'm coming.
Osman is going to Nikea.
He'll see governor Manuel.
We can't let this happen.
This is going to be his last voyage.
We'll ambush him.
He is not taking Nikea path though.
He took precautions.
He'll take Kizilcahisar path.
It's where we end him.
So your pigeons brough news.
I will undertake this mission.
Does anyone object?
You have to go with an army, Nicola.
Take Catalans with you.
I want to make sure he is dead.
There's more.
Osman is not going to take the holy relic
with him.
He'll leave it in his tent.
While you rip his lungs off, I'll
grab the holy relic from his tent!
I will kill everyone who stands in my way!
How are you going to do this?
You'll see.
A dead Bey, a tent without a leader...
Finally, the end of the Turks is coming.
We are going to attack at the right time
and right place.
Not only Osman, Turgut should
live the same destiny!
Nicola, Turks are dangerous when
they have a leader.
However, Turks without a leader
are even more dangerous.
What is your offer Kosses?
While you are busy destroying them...
I'll choose their leader.
Which means I am going to
pull Turgut on our side.
Turks...
...follow their leaders.
If we have Turgut...
we have Turks as well.
That's right.
So we agree.
No!
Thank Allah
Thank Allah, we are going to see
my child wearing this Inshallah.
Inshallah, my Osman.
Inshallah.
When I go away without you...
I always think of returning and...
dreaming your beautiful eyes.
I imagine you coming back and
hold onto that dream...
and wait for you.
Our children and our people are entrusted
to Allah first, then you.
I'm going to protect what you entrusted me
just like I protect my love for you, my Osman.
My Bala.
No one is leaving without taking an
oath to this agreement.
We fell out with each other
because of Osman so many times.
With an oath, we are going to bless
our unity that we build today.
My friends.
I took an oath to Caesar, Rogatus.
I am not going to hesitate to take an oath
to Jesus.
It's high time that we exiled Turks
from this country.
It's time to unite.
I swear on holy Jesus.
I am going to be loyal
to this unity forever.
And in order to dispel Turks...
I am going to fight until the last
drop of my blood!
Mother, can I come in?
Come daughter.
Aygül.
Welcome daughter.
I wanted to have your blessings before
leaving.
Give me your blessings, mother.
I give my blessings to you, daughter.
Come back at once, Inshallah.
Aygül.
There's something else, huh?
Come here.
Sit down.
Tell me.
No trouble is unsolvable with Allah.
Show me a way, mother.
Both my head and heart are unclear.
What's it, inshallah?
Tell me my Aygül.
Cerkutay.
Cerkutay wants to marry me.
That's not a trouble.
Be happy, daughter.
why are you sad?
Cerkutay is a good man.
He is brave.
He is merciful.
He makes me smile when I don't.
So?
But...
You know what I went through, mother.
I cannot trust anyone.
I am afraid.
My father from my blood first...
...then the betrayal of the man
that they made me marry.
Everyone I leant on has fallen.
I have been leaning only
on myself since then...
so that I don't fall.
Your tongue and heart talk differently, huh?
Aygül.
You like that crazy boy, don't you?
Our ancestor said "People are diverse
just like the land"
Why are you shutting your door to everyone
just because some people betrayed you?
Go out now, observe anyone in the tent.
Everyone is different.
Our prophet said "women and men are the
two parts of one whole."
You have gone through a lot.
You ended up with a bad guy
that didn't suit you.
What if Allah's plan is to heal your
wound with Cerkutay...
and complete Cerkutay with you?
Huh?
Allah granted that man with mercy.
He turned his back on the cruels,
became an Alp to Osman Bey.
Listen to me, daughter.
Think twice.
I will think about it mother.
I am going to think about it again.
My beautiful daughter.
I am glad that I have you, mother.
I am glad that you are here.
Always, daughter.
Always.
Alps that Turgut sent to follow us.
The last face they see will be
Anselmo's face.
Let them go.
Let's see if they can go back to
their tent now.
It's not enough to blind Turks, Anselmo.
You have to kill them.
You have to kill Turks.
You...must...kill...kill them Anselmo!
We are going to kill Osman, Anselmo.
Are you ready for it?
We are already late, Nicola.
I swear that today is going
to their last day.
May Allah grant you with victory.
Thank you Bala.
Thank you.
Masha Allah (praise be).
Masha Allah my son.
Mother.
Go well and return well, son.
May Allah open your way.
Amin mother.
Amin.
May Allah bless you Bala Hatun.
My Bey, we brought the gifts.
We are waiting for your command.
Ride the horses.
Go!
Bilecik Castle.
Nicola is after Osman, your guys
will infiltrate into Kayi tent.
What a nice day.
Rogatus, you haven't told me how
you are going to infiltrate into Kayi tent.
Lord Rogatus.
Lord Kosses.
I am Julia.
Here is the person who'll bring death
to Osman's tribe.
Magnificus.
(Splendid)
Class act.
How is this beautiful angel going
to manage everything by herself, Rogatus?
Who said I am alone, Lord Kosses?
We are an army.
Our name is the angels of death.
The angels of death.
Nice. So, how are the angels of death...
going to infiltrate into Kayi tent?
Dodurgalı!
He is a Turkish merchant.
He is going to deliver oil to Osman's tent.
Now I understand.
Meanwhile, our beautiful
angel will possess our relic
By killing every Turk standing on her way.
So, what about this one?
He is fine.
It's a simple poison.
He will die if he is not treated
for a while.
Very nice.
I want you to use this while carrying
death to Osman's tribe.
Whatever you say.
- Goktug!
- Yes my Bey.
- Are the horses shoed?
We'll take Kızılhisar path.
The infidels must have heard that
we are on our way to Iznik.
The infidels think they set up a game
but my Bey ruins them!
Let's go!
We don't have time to waste.
They are not aware that they are
riding their beloved horses to death!
Not only Osman, we are going to
end them all, Anselmo!
This land will be covered with
Turkish blood today.
Don't doubt that.
Come, Osman Bey.
Come.
Investigate.
Yes my Bey.
Water.
We'll bring now.
Osman!
Malhun!
Bala.
What's it, daughter?
Are you okay?
I am okay.
But I felt something bad.
May Allah end it up well, Inshallah.
Osman!
He is not hungry.
Why is he not sleeping?
My Bey!
- Alps!
- Osman!
Malhun.
Attack!
Catalans!
Allah-u Aqbar
(Allah is the greatest)
Osman!
Protect my children, my Allah.
My son sleeps well...
He sleeps, he grows up...
Before the birds return
His father will come
- Osman!
- Malhun!
Infidel dog!
Come to me, come!
Finally!
My Bey!
Die already! Die already!
Die!
In the forest we haunt down the jackals
who set a trap on the path
Retreat!
Osman!
Don't let him run away!
- Osman, are you okay?
- I am fine.
Osman!
Don't let him run away!
Follow him!
Malhun.
Let's go.
Let's do it Malhun!
Are you fine, brother?
My wound is okay, Boran
but I am not okay.
Being okay is haram until
I kill them!
Sure brother, sure.
We must find my Bey first.
- Let's search now!
- Let's go!
- My Bey!
- Cerkutay.
Cerkutay!
Cerkutay stop!
Stop!
I'll bandage your wound.
The big wound here cannot be bandaged.
- My Bey!
- You are going to bleed to death!
Cerkutay won't die!
Especially...
not before finding his Bey.
You Allah-sent crazy!
- My Bey!
- Cerkutay!
Any sign?
No.
You don't have one either I guess.
This forest shall be my grave if I leave
without finding my Bey!
If they did something to my Bey...
I'll be chasing them with my
two blades!
Don't talk nonsense, Cerkutay!
Catalan dogs cannot hurt my Bey!
Shut up! Malhun Hatun is with them.
I hope we find them safe and sound.
The forest is large!
Don't stand!
Aygül, Aygül, stop.
We can't split, brothers.
The infidels are everywhere.
You are right.
We won't stop until we find our Bey!
We'll search till dawn!
Brothers, keep your eyes open.
Both for our Bey and the enemy!
Let's go!
Let's go.
Where are you headed?
Many will bleed today.
You are the one to die if
someone has to.
I have been waiting for this
moment for days, Osman.
Come to me, Anselmo.
Don't be afraid.
Malhun.
Everytime I raise my sword...
You were there.
You killed my Alps.
You intended to kill my unborn
child...
and my Hatuns.
Now...
Your time is up.
Find them!
Hurry!
Let's go.
Argos!
You take men and keep searching back.
Do not come without Osman!
Do not!
Today I'll see Osman dead right here.
Yes sir!
You two! Come with me!
Keep on!
How?
How did that man manage to do this
in that situation?
How?
He is not dying.
Why is that man not dying?
Why?
He is not dying.
That man is not dying!
He is not dying!
Search everywhere!
Split and search everywhere!
Everywhere! Everywhere! Everywhere!
Why is he not dying?
This man is not dying!
He is not dying!
Osman, Osman!
Osman.
Osman, Osman, Osman.
Osman hold on, hold on.
We have to go.
Hang on!
Osman, hang on.
Hold onto me. Hold onto me.
Come on.
Somewhere...
Somewhere like a cave...
...we must find.
Osman.
Harmankaya Castle.
Destroying both Osman and his tent
at the same time.
This is going to end Turks.
Osman will die.
He will die but...
I don't want to struggle with Turks
after Osman dies.
This is where you step in, Mari.
- Turgut.
- Turgut, ya.
We must pull him on our side.
How are you going to do it?
Everyone likes power, brother.
I'll promise him power.
He is brave enough to replace Osman,
and as ambitious has him.
I am sure he'll accept this.
You'll go to Turgut first thing
in the morning.
I trust you Mari.
Don't worry, Turgut is in my hand.
Nice.
Osman.
Okay, hold on.
Hold on.
Easy, Osman.
Make a fire.
Sit down, my Osman.
Osman.
Make a fire.
Come on, make a fire.
Hurry!
Osman, my Osman!
I am here.
I cannot wait, come on!
Hurry!
Osman, Osman.
Hold on Osman.
O the Healer!
Hold on my Osman!
Okay, okay, come.
Hold on to me.
Hold on.
Hold on Osman.
Wait.
Osman.
O the Healer! O the Healer!
Allah heals.
My Allah, give Osman more power.
Give Osman more power.
Polytheists set many traps for
Allah's messenger.
Our prophet firstly took caution...
then trusted in Allah.
In Battle of the Trench,
the trenches...
were precaution.
When the polytheists attempted
to take his sacred life...
taking the hard road instead of
the short road...
and taking shelter in...
Sevr Cave with his friend
Hz.Ebubakir...
was a precaution.
But despite all these precautions...
the most talented trackers
of the polytheists...
came all the way to the
entrance of that cave.
And even a crumble of fear...
wasn't present in our prophet's heart.
Because in the verse that came for
him, Allah said...
''and Allah too plans...
but the best of planners is Allah.''
We believe that...
the best of planners is Allah.
And he is always with
his subjects.
In this world, neither the tyrants nor
tyranny will end.
When Muslims take precautions
and trust in Allah...
all plans made by the tyrants can
be deflected.
My Orhan.
My son.
Osman!
You are alright.
Thank Allah.
I'm fine.
What about you?
As long as you are good...
nothing will happen to me.
My Orhan.
You are wounded.
It's not important, Osman.
Malhun...
We need to burn it.
I'll do it.
Just get some rest.
We need to burn it.
Come on.
Alright. Slowly.
Slowly. Slowly.
Don't tire yourself.
With the name of Allah.
My brave wife.
Come.
Osman.
As long as I have you...
nothing can take me down.
True.
Thank you.
Always...
you stand behind me like a mountain.
I never get down.
Never.
You lighten up the darkness.
You do.
True.
With Allah's help, we'll
get out of here too.
We will find our alps.
The heathens who try to stop us...
will lose their lives.
We won't let them run away.
We will, Osman.
Inshallah.
Bilecik Castle
Ever since the day Turks killed me
parents, I waited for this day, Rogatus.
I didn't spend a day without thinking
about killing them.
That's why I trained the
Death Angels.
They all were born to kill.
I know, Julia.
You are an amazing warrior and
so are your soldiers.
But your greatest weapon is
your revenge.
My family died to keep the
Turks out of these lands.
I will finish what they left
unfinished.
I will take them out of these lands.
Show me a target.
I wouldn't find anyone better for
this job.
Soon, you will get your revenge, Julia.
My Allah.
I take shelter under you against
every trouble.
You found a cure for Job's
merciless nuisance.
You let Jonah live in a fish's belly.
You took Joseph out of that well.
You protected our holy and sacred prophet
Muhammed against the polytheists.
In the cave he hid in, you protected him
with a bird's egg and a spider web.
O' my merciful Allah!
For your prophets and saints....
help us. Destine us to find my
alps safe and sound.
Destine us to take the revenge
of our martyrs.
We have no other door to knock.
Don't return us empty-handed, my Allah!
Amin, my Allah.
Amin.
Bilecik Castle
Even if the earth goes down,
justice will prevail.
Turks.
I will end you with my own hands.
You took my family from me.
I won't die before taking everything
from you.
You will die, Turks!
You all will die!
And it will be my poison that caused it.
Osman Bey said that he will buy the
rest of the goods and compensate.
The first group will come today,
inshallah.
Thank Allah, Osman Bey is the hope
of all Turkmens.
They might want to take advantage
from Osman Bey's absence.
We don't have just one enemy.
Don't drop your guard, Gündüz.
Mother, don't worry.
Alps will be careful.
We are here too.
Be at ease.
No one will survive!
I'm working for Rogatus, you know it.
You will live because you
will help us.
Rogatus and Kosses are waiting for us.
Hurry!
Come on!
Slowly.
Despite all the caution,
they ambushed us!
There is a traitor in the tribe.
We need to return to the tribe
at once then!
No.
The tribe has many protectors.
We will move forward.
But we need to find the alps first.
Like this, my bey? You are on your feet
but you aren't alright.
I won't return empty-handed.
The people await good news.
Alright but which way will we
go, my bey?
It's a huge forest!
We'll find it, Malhun.
We'll find it.
Cerkutay.
My lion must've thought something.
Come on.
Brother. Did you find a track?
No.
No trace.
If we can't find our bey.
Let him find us, brothers.
Come on!
My crazy brother.
Well done, Rogatus.
Your carpenters did a really good job.
Now the only thing to do is take over
those carts to enter Kayı Tribe.
And that was your pretty angel's task.
Do you think they did it?
You shouldn't be doubting after
yesterday's show, Kosses.
And they should've been here, Rogatus.
Here they are.
Are you sure it's them, Rogatus?
Aren't they Turkmens?
Dear lords.
We are ready to enter the tribe.
What about poison?
It's ready, as you ordered.
It will be the end of every Turk
that stands in my way.
As I see, you also completed
your preperations.
Of course.
Lestor will accompany you.
So, only thing left to do is to become
the nightmare of Osman's tribe.
-Turgut Bey.
-Mari. What are you doing here?
I'm here by my brother Michael Kosses's
orders.
What does your brother want?
Did he send you instead of
coming here?
Is he that afraid?
Michael Kosses isn't afraid of anyone,
Turgut Bey.
And about my visitation.
Are you alright, Osman?
I'm fine.
Alps!
Alps left a track.
They are alive, Malhun!
They are alive.
We are getting closer, inshallah.
Mashallah to my lions.
Mashallah.
Come on.
I didn't realize it when I first came
here. Your tribe is small.
It is.
Osman Bey's tribe is magnificent.
It is more ordinate compared to yours.
Oh, you Byzantines...
Come to the point, Mari.
Why are you here?
We want to replace this bloody hostility
with an agreement that pleases both sides.
My brother Michael Kosses
wants to do trade with you.
So, both you and your small tribe
will win.
After all the blood...
he wants to be our friend?
I advice you to forget the past and
start again stronger, Turgut Bey.
What you call the past and tell me to
forget are my martyr alps.
I won't forget it.
But the condition of my tribe is
apparent.
Remembering it doesn't stop
me from doing trade.
For their well-being, I will
consider it.
I'm guessing that you are a smart man.
I'm sure that you'll make the right call.
But know it, my conditions
will be heavy.
Let's talk about them when you
make your decision.
I'll be waiting.
Now, if you allow me.
Turgut Bey.
-Yes.
-I almost forgot.
This is for you.
Please.
I thought it would fit a bey like you.
Thank you, Mari.
You...
don't look like a man to stay
under someone else's shadow...
Turgut Bey.
What does she want, my bey?
Kosses wants to trade.
What are you saying, my bey?
Working with the heathens?
Osman Bey has been doing politics
for so long.
Why shouldn't we?
My bey...
Where are you, my bey?
Where are you?
Split out, brothers!
Come on!
My bey!
Thank Allah!
-My bey!
-Alps!
My bey!
My bey, thank Allah!
Are you alright?
Thank Allah!
Are you alright, my bey?
I'm alright.
Thank Allah for this.
Are you alright?
As long as you are well, nothing can
happen to us, my bey.
I should've known that they can't do
anything to you, my bey.
-Aygül.
-My bey.
-Malhun Hatun, are you alright?
-I'm good, Göktuğ.
Who knows how you slaughtered that
dog Anselmo.
Where is Gencebey?
He is waiting for us at the horses.
But my bey, you have many wounds.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
I'm alright.
The swords they swing at us are
destined to go blunt.
Thank Allah, we are alright.
Mashallah, my bey.
Then, let's go to the horses.
Alright, my bey.
-Let's search it well, brother.
-Alright, brother.
No offence, brother.
Let me.
Brother. Get down.
Brother.
Tie them well next time.
They were going to be spilled and wasted.
Alright.
Go on.
Go on!
Alps!
Hold on! You are riding the wrong way.
We are going to İznik.
We won't sheath our swords until
we reach the destination.
As you order, my bey.
Come on.
Mashallah, he is appetent.
Mashallah to my lion.
My Orhan!
Bala?
You are thinking about Osman Bey,
don't you?
I feel suffocated.
Whatever I did wasn't enough to
let it go.
Think well so that all can be well.
Come on, don't let Orhan get cold.
Come on, Bala.
Tell me, where is this oil from?
-It's from Karailyas.
-Is that so?
I know their oil well.
It's really good.
What is this? Huh? It's nothing
like their oil?
Crops weren't good this year, I see?
Selcan Hatun, not all can be the same.
This is how it is this year.
Alright then. Price it accordingly.
-Good day.
-Thank you.
I was so close.
I was so close, he was in my hands!
He was in my hands!
But then again, again, again
he ran away!
Osman...
He was in my hands! If he is in your
hands, you squeeze I'm like a fly!
Like a fly!
Where will you run, Osman Bey?
Where?
This is my land!
This is my mountain!
This is my city!
These castles are my castles!
These cities are mine!
I'm Ceaser's son!
Aya Nikola!
And you are mine too, Osman Bey.
You are mine!
Do you know what I will do to you?
I will cut off your hands, your feet...
your fingers...
I'll put you in a cage with your
beloved animals...
wolves and jackals.
I'll make them eat you bit by bit.
But this would be a weak ending for you.
It would be a weak ending for you.
Do you know what I will do to you?
I will hold you on your skull...
and put you on the back of my horse.
I'll walk you around all the Turkmen
tribes.
I'll tell them to look!
Look, look!
Here's the head of the one who
stood up against Aya Nikola!
Osman Bey!
This is your blood!
Osman Bey, I will make you choke blood!
Whenever someone of your lineage
thinks of rebellion...
someone of my lineage will...
smash his head like this.
Don't...
don't think that you won
this war.
Don't!
Don't think that you've beaten me!
This war...
will be over tonight, Osman Bey.
Tonight.
You get it, Argos?
I get it, sir.
We are going to Harmankaya.
İznik Castle
Welcome, Saguros. What news did
you bring from Constantinople?
I have great news, Manuel.
The emperor congratulates you
for your services.
Now, you need to rest.
Forever.
Will you overthrow me in front of
my loyal soldiers?
In these lands, the emperor always
has the last word.
Soldiers, help Governor Saguros leave.
Soldiers!
Not only your loyal soldiers, Manuel.
Everyone in your city is under my
command now.
You were my friend.
Friendship. Friendship surrenders
to ambition.
You shouldn't have put your eyes
on the emperor's throne.
This isn't true. You did it.
You deceived the emperor!
It's what the emperor believes.
Harmankaya Castle
I'm grateful that you forgot all the
trouble you had and came here.
Turgut Bey.
Nothing is forgotten, Kosses.
Mari knows.
I'm doing it for my tribe's well-being.
And for all the Turkmens.
You will be facing us when you
agree with us.
When was Osman Bey with me that
I should fear that?
From now, you are responsible for our
caravans' security.
They'll pass through your lands and
they'll be under your responsibiilty.
Of course, since we are in a tough
the situation, we'll be generous.
The health of our agreement depends
on how generous you are, Kosses.
For every caravan that reaches its
destination safely.
You will get half of what
we earn.
A reasonable offer.
I wouldn't accept any less.
I take this as a yes.
We'll get stronger together.
I'm glad that we have an agreement.
If you stand with me, I'm a really
nice guy, Kosses.
As long as you don't face me.
Then, let it be good for everyone.
I hope so.
Nikola.
İznik Castle
Welcome, Osman Bey.
I knew you were coming.
Thank you.
Thank you, but...
I thought we were going to see
Governor Manuel.
The Emperor resigned him.
My name is Saguros.
I'm the new governor of Nikea.
So...
what happened to you?
They tried to stop us.
But we let them know that
we can't be stopped.
Catalonians and Lord Nikola...
they ambushed us.
Even though they knew that you were
coming to Nikea?
What insolence is this?
The hostility of the lords
isn't a secret.
But assuring the security of the roads
is your job.
Fortunately, they made a mistake
by facing us.
We slaughtered all the Catalonians.
Now, your roads are safe.
I think you didn't come here to clean
the roads of Nikea.
Since Manuel and the lords
broke the agreement...
I'm not letting...
a single caravan enter your lands.
When I opened the city treasury,
I saw that it was empty.
He spent everything he has to
feed his people.
You must know it well...
that you should stand with me...
not against me.
Don't. Don't.
Don't make the same mistakes
with Manuel.
Go on, Osman Bey.
Someone who just got to their position
should please the folk.
Otherwise, his reign won't last long.
Are you threatening me?
I'm saying the truth.
The surety of your position...
depends on the trade you will
do with me.
Otherwise, I won't stop raiding
your caravans.
War is a wedding for the Turks!
Speaking this boldly...
in my castle full of my soldiers...
And also, you have your wife
with you.
We say that war is a wedding
for the Turks.
Not for the men.
Women are no different than men.
We aren't afraid.
You are right.
So, what's your offer?
Whatever you get from...
your trade with the lords,
I'll give you double.
We've come from a tough road.
All our gifts are wasted.
For this reason.
I want to give you this as a token.
Kayı Tribe will provide all the needs
of İznik.
I will personally protect the caravans.
Where the Turks exist...
there is no other way than
making an agreement.
Know it.
Call the clerk. We'll make an agreement
with Osman Bey.
Look at you, Gencebey.
You went to your homelands.
You caught up with your parents.
You rode your horse from Karabağ
to here to fight in battle.
Don't you ever get tired?
Thank you, Cerkutay. Thank you.
Now I'm catching up with my brothers.
I missed fighting alongside my bey.
Until our horses die and our blood
gets dry, we are behind Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Harmankaya Castle
Osman.
I said this is it.
This is it.
Then again, again, again he ran
away from me. Again!
How could he?
Tell me, Nikola!
From that ambush, among all those
soldiers, how did he get out alive?
I wounded him deeply, Kosses!
I said I won't return before seeing
him dead!
And I didn't!
I followed him for a day!
Then, then he faced me...
and fought.
This man isn't dying.
He isn't dying.
He isn't.
He isn't dying, Kosses.
Nikola, we thought of this
possibility.
When he returns, the funerals of
his loved ones will be waiting.
I swore an oath. He will feel
that pain before dying.
He won't!
He won't die.
Of course, I also thought that Osman
could run away.
I have a spy in İznik.
The woman is working in the governor's
kitchen.
And she knows that Osman is coming.
She is very talented with poisons.
I gave her a lot of gold for her to
prepare a good ending for Osman.
Possibilities, Rogatus.
Possibilities, Kosses.
You never give up, Nikola.
This makes you a scary enemy...
and a good ally.
We tried it many times with
swords.
I couldn't let him live anymore.
Tell us, Nikola.
What poison is this?
It's a poison strong enough to kill a
horse in a very short time.
Even a horse!
İznik Castle
Now we passed the merchants and
the lords, my bey.
We used to give the governor
a carpet before.
Now, we are providing all
his needs.
When he sends his caravans safely,
it'll be heard from everywhere.
They'll hear that our lands are safe.
We have prosperity.
We are growing day by day, Osman Bey.
May Allah destine you and your
lineage even better days.
Amin, Malhun. Amin.
I wouldn't let you go like this,
Osman Bey.
And also, we need to celebrate
our agreement.
Go on.
Sadaqallahulazim.
Soon, my Orhan.
Soon you will reunite with your
mother and father.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
It's not the time for a change of guards.
What is this, brothers?
Who are you?
Didn't you like it?
Sherbets are here.
Now, we are friends, Osman Bey.
Everything on the table is made
according to your religion's rules.
All the meat is bought from
Muslim butchers.
Please.
Go on.
If you say that it's halal.
Then...
Let us enjoy it.
With the name of Allah.
Thank you, my bey.
I also want Sherbet.
Come on.
With the name of Allah.
Where is this?
So, you were protecting it.
I will kill you all!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com